Guide to the Hill Family Papers, 1662-1994 (bulk 1835-1970)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Elsie M. Hill, 1875-1994
  - Subseries B. Subject Files - Social and Political Activism
    - Social and political activism in Connecticut
      - Connecticut Tercentenary, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 655)
      - U.S. Congressman’s reports to Connecticut constituents, 1962-1970, undated (Box 9, Folder 656)
      - Connecticut miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 657)
      - Connecticut miscellaneous (deteriorated, from folders 651-653), 1925-1968, undated (Box 18, Folder 1110)
    - Lockwood-Mathews Mansion, Norwalk
      - Correspondence; meeting minutes of the Citizens Actions Committee and the Common Interest Groups of Norwalk; and public hearings, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 658)
      - Correspondence; meeting minutes of the Citizens Action Committee and the Common Interest Group of Norwalk; and public hearings, 1964-1972, undated (Box 9, Folder 659)
      - Contents of scrapbook presented to EH by Common Interest Group, undated (Box 9, Folder 660-662)
      - Articles about mansion in Mark, the Community Magazine (Norwalk), 1960-1967 (Box 9, Folder 663)
      - Miscellaneous articles about the mansion, 1959-1967 (Box 9, Folder 664)
      - Miscellaneous pamphlets and brochures about the mansion, undated (Box 9, Folders 665-666)
      - Lockwood and Mathews family histories, undated (Box 9, Folder 667)
      - Miscellaneous notes about the mansion, undated (Box 9, Folders 668-670)
  - Subseries C. Subject Files – Biographical Materials
    - General
      - Biographical notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 671)
      - Broadcasts and personal appearances, undated (Box 9, Folder 672)
      - Broadcasts and personal appearances (deteriorated), undated (Box 18, Folder 1111)
      - Employment material, undated (Box 9, Folder 673)
      - Passports [including picture of Elsie Hill and Leslie Hill-Lévitt Latham], birth certificate facsimiles, social security cards, other personal material, undated (Box 9, Folder 674)
      - Personal realia, undated (Box 9, Folder 675)
      - Realia relating to the women's movement, undated (Box 9, Folder 676)
      - New York-Moscow flight, 1968 Jul 15 (Box 9, Folder 677-678)
    - Education
      - High school French notebook, 1899 (Box 10, Folder 679)
      - Notebooks from Paris and Rome, 1900-1901 (Box 10, Folder 680)
      - Vassar notes: American history, undated (Box 10, Folder 681)
      - Vassar notes: Biology, circa 1902-1904 (Box 10, Folder 682-684)
      - Vassar notes: Charities and Corrections, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 685)
      - Vassar notes: Comparative anatomy of vertebrates, 1905 Fall (Box 10, Folder 686)
      - Vassar notes: Economic history, undated (Box 10, Folder 687)
      - Vassar notes: English, 1903 (Box 10, Folder 688)
      - Vassar notes: blank French notebook, undated (Box 10, Folder 689)
      - Vassar notes: Latin, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 690)
      - Vassar notes: Miscellaneous, 1904-1905 (Box 10, Folder 691)
      - Vassar notes: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 10, Folder 692)
      - Vassar [?] notes: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 10, Folder 693)
      - Vassar notes: Municipal and house sanitation notes, circa 1905 (Box 10, Folder 694)
      - Vassar notes: Psychology, undated (Box 10, Folder 695)
      - Vassar [?] notes: Religion, 1904 Jun-Jul (Box 10, Folder 696)
      - Vassar College catalog, 1902-1903 (Box 10, Folder 697)
      - Vassar College catalog, 1905-1906 (Box 10, Folder 698)
      - Contents of EMH's "Memory book" of Vassar College, 1899-1902 (Box 10, Folders 699-704)
      - Contents of EMH's "Memory book" of Vassar College [incl. letter from C. Fink], 1903 (Box 10, Folders 705-710)
      - Contents of EMH's "Memory book" of Vassar College, 1904-1906 (Box 10, Folders 711-714)
      - Contents of EMH's "Memory book" of Vassar College: Commencement invitations, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 715)
      - Vassar College miscellanea, 1900-1916 (Box 11, Folder 716)
      - Vassar College miscellanea, 1964, undated (Box 11, Folder 717)
      - Vassar Alumnae directories, 1962-1963, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 718)
      - Miscellaneous Vassar alumnae communications, 1951-1969, undated (Box 11, Folder 719)
      - Associated Vassar Clubs of Fairfield County [CT], 1960-1966 (Box 11, Folder 720)
      - Communication of Vassar College Class of 1906, 1933-1969 (Box 11, Folder 721)
      - Vassar College Class of 1906 memorabilia, circa 1906 (Box 11, Folder 722)
      - Vassar College certificate, 1906; (rolled) (Box 41)
      - New York School of Philanthropy, 1906 Summer (Box 11, Folder 723)
      - George Washington University. Notebook for Property I. Personal, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 724)
      - Yale Law School. Assignments and exams, undated (Box 12, Folder 725)
      - Yale Law School. Introduction to the Study of Law [textbook], undated (Box 12, Folder 726)
      - Study of Law: Notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 727-730)
      - Yale Law School: Notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 731-731B)
  - Subseries D. Subject Files – Non-Political Affiliations
    - Ancestral Societies
      - Annual meeting programs, undated (Box 11, Folder 732)
      - Charters and by-laws, undated (Box 11, Folder 733)
      - Society communications with members, 1939-1966, undated (Box 11, Folder 734)
      - D.A.R. manual for citizenship, undated (Box 11, Folder 735)
      - D.A.R. notebook, undated (Box 11, Folder 736)
      - Meeting notices, 1939-1969, undated (Box 11, Folder 737)
      - Membership allocations, undated (Box 11, Folder 738)
      - Membership cards, undated (Box 11, Folder 739)
      - Membership lists, undated (Box 11, Folder 740)
      - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 741)
      - Ephemera, 1932-1970, undated (Box 11, Folder 742)
      - Sash and badges, undated (Box 11, Folder 743)
      - Yearbooks and calendars, 1934-1969 (Box 11, Folder 744-747)
    - Joel Barlow
      - A bill authorizing the erection of a memorial to Joel Barlow, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 748)
      - Addresses given at the Joel Barlow Commemoration, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 749)
      - Programs for the Joel Barlow Commemoration, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 750)
      - Notes about Joel Barlow and the Joel Barlow Commemoration, undated (Box 12, Folder 751)
      - Notebook on Joel Barlow, undated (Box 12, Folder 752)
      - Notes and transcriptions of Joel Barlow's works, 1931-1935, undated (Box 12, Folder 753)
      - Copyright denial for "Frontispiece for the 'Hasty Pudding',", undated (Box 12, Folder 754)
      - Speeches about Joel Barlow, 1935-1960, undated (Box 12, Folder 755)
      - Articles about Joel Barlow, 1938-1967 (Box 12, Folder 756)
      - Fritz, Florence. Joel Barlow's Early Deistic Liberalism [thesis], undated (Box 12, Folder 757)
      - Miscellaneous Barlow facsimiles, undated (Box 12, Folder 758)
    - Genealogy
      - Genealogical notes on Joel Barlow and the Barlow family, undated (Box 12, Folder 759)
      - Genealogy of Alice Stone Blackwell, researched by Katherine Stetson Chamberlin, undated (Box 12, Folder 760)
      - Genealogical notes of the Hill, Mosman, Goodale and Rice families, 1940-1969, undated (Box 12, Folder 761)
    - Goat Raising
      - Pedigrees, 1929-1931 (Box 12, Folder 762)
      - Miscellanea, 1929-1935, undated (Box 12, Folder 763)
  - Subseries E. Clippings
    - Social and Political Activism
      - Suffrage, 1913-1970, undated (Box 12, Folders 764-768)
      - Equal Rights Amendment, 1921-1971, undated (Box 12, Folders 769-773)
      - International Women's Rights, 1925-1966, undated (Box 12, Folders 774-776)
      - Other women's concerns and interests, 1907-1939 (Box 12, Folders 777-780)
      - Other women's concerns and interests, 1940-1966, undated (Box 13, Folders 781-785)
      - Miscellaneous politics and government, 1912-1970, undated (Box 13, Folders 786-794)
      - Civil rights and segregation, 1957-1969, undated (Box 13, Folder 795)
      - Prohibition, 1928-1966, undated (Box 13, Folder 796)
      - War and military service, 1916, undated (Box 13, Folder 797)
    - Connecticut Social and Political Interests
      - Connecticut politics and government, 1922-1970, undated (Box 13, Folders 798-800)
      - Connecticut zoning and roads, 1929-1967, undated (Box 13, Folder 801)
      - Connecticut land preservation and building restoration, 1958-1969, undated (Box 13, Folder 802)
      - Dissolution of the Gilbert Farm, 1930-1940, undated (Box 13, Folder 803)
      - Preservation of the Lockwood-Mathews Mansion, Norwalk, 1958-1976, undated (Box 13, Folders 804-805)
      - Sherwood Island State Park, Westport, 1929-1964, undated (Box 13, Folders 806-810)
      - Connecticut education system, 1914-1969, undated (Box 13, Folders 811-812)
    - Biographical Clippings of Elsie Hill
      - General, arranged chronologically, 1913-1994, undated (Box 13, Folders 813-818)
    - Personal Interests
      - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1929-1970, undated (Box 13, Folders 819-820)
      - Goats, 1929-1932 (Box 13, Folder 821)
      - Historic preservation, 1933-1969, undated (Box 13, Folder 822-823)
      - Joel Barlow, 1931-1976 (Box 13, Folders 824-825)
    - Magazine articles on women's rights
      - General, 1911-1954 (Box 13, Folder 826)
      - General, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 827)
      - General, 1964-1969, undated (Box 13, Folder 828)
      - "If You Ask Me" by E. Roosevelt, McCall's, 1949 Jun (Box 13, Folder 829)
  - Subseries F. Manuscripts and Notes
    - List of series of Elsie Hill speeches, 1906-1936 (Box 13, Folder 830)
    - [On "Chiffon Politics"], 1912 (Box 13, Folder 831)
    - The Mother as Creative Artist [notes], [1926?] (Box 13, Folder 832)
    - The Mother as Creative Artist [typed drafts], 1926 (Box 13, Folder 833)
    - In Defense of Congressmen [notes], [1928] (Box 13, Folder 834)
    - In Defense of Congressmen [typescripts], [1928] (Box 13, Folder 835)
    - [Alice Paul], [1930?] (Box 13, Folder 836)
    - The World Court or World Code, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 837)
    - [Regarding the World Court appropriations bill], [1932] (Box 13, Folder 838)
    - [Regarding the World Court appropriations bill] (deteriorated), [1932] (Box 18, Folder 1112)
    - [On the Independent Republican Party of Connecticut], [1932] (Box 13, Folder 839)
    - [Campaign speech], [1932] (Box 13, Folder 840)
    - Hello, Connecticut [campaign speech draft], [1932] (Box 13, Folder 841)
    - Daughters of the American Evolution, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 842)
    - Yankees Born Again or Yankees Reborn o Yankees of Power and Light, [circa 1934] (Box 13, Folder 843)
    - The March of the Women or Women of Power and Light, [circa 1937] (Box 13, Folder 844)
    - Women of Power and Light, [circa 1937] (Box 13, Folder 845)
    - [Script of "We the People" broadcast], [circa 1939 Nov 10] (Box 13, Folder 846)
    - [Speech given at meeting of D.C. College Equal Suffrage League], 1940 (Box 13, Folder 847)
    - On the English Common Law Status of women [transcript of radio broadcast], 1948 (Box 13, Folder 848)
    - Miscellaneous drafts of speeches, circa 1949, undated (Box 13, Folder 849)
    - Miracle of America, no.6: Woman's Suffrage [transcript of a play broadcast on KOWL Santa Monica, CA], 1951 (Box 13, Folder 850)
    - Little Girls Grow Up, [1951] (Box 13, Folder 851)
    - [Partial script for broadcast of Persona Report: Elsie Hill in conversation with Edith Evans Astbury], 1964 (Box 13, Folder 852)
    - [Speech given at meeting of the Common Interest Group of Norwalk], [circa 1967] (Box 13, Folder 853)
    - [Speeches given at meeting of the Connecticut Branch of the NWP], undated (Box 13, Folder 854)
    - "Women as Dishwashers,", undated (Box 13, Folder 855)
    - [Miscellaneous poetry manuscripts by various and anonymous writers], undated (Box 13, Folder 856)
    - [Miscellaneous poetry manuscripts by various and anonymous writers] (deteriorated), undated (Box 18, Folder 1112)
    - Miscellaneous notes and statements, undated (Box 18, Folders 857-859)
    - Miscellaneous notes and statements (deteriorated, from folders 856, 858), undated (Box 18, Folder 1112)
    - Miscellaneous press releases, [1923-1937] (Box 18, Folder 860)
    - Notebooks with miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 18, Folders 861-862)
  - Subseries G. Diaries, Calendars, Address Books, and Telephone Lists
    - Biographical diaries, 1883-1928 (Box 11, Folders 863-865)
    - Diaries, 1907-1927 (Box 11, Folders 866-871)
    - Diaries, 1928-1939 (Box 14, Folders 872-877)
    - Diaries, 1942-1959 (Box 14, Folders 878-880)
    - Address books, undated (Box 14, Folder 881)
    - Miscellaneous addresses and telephone numbers, undated (Box 14, Folders 882-883)
    - Calendars, 1930-1963 (Box 14, Folders 884-895)
    - Calendars, 1964-1968 (Box 14, Folders 896-905)
    - Correspondence, 1903-1929; (172 letters) (Box 14, Folders 906-912)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1948 (Box 14, Folders 913-915)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1971, undated (Box 15, Folders 916-920)
    - Correspondence (deteriorated, from folder 906), 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1086)
    - Correspondence re: The Rock Lot, 1940-1969; (119 letters) (Box 15, Folders 921-927)
    - Miscellaneous notes re: The Rock Lot, 1923-1940 (Box 15, Folder 928)
    - Estate of Annie H. Thomas, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 929)
    - Estate of Ebenezer J. Hill, 1899-1918 (Box 15, Folder 930)
    - Estate of Mary E. M. Hill, 1918-1919 (Box 15, Folder 931)
    - Will of Clara Mossman Hill, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 932)
    - Records of investments, 1924-1930 (Box 15, Folder 933-934)
    - Stocks and bonds, 1920-1955, undated (Box 15, Folder 935)
    - Mortgages, deeds and leases, 1875-1968 (Box 15, Folders 936-937)
    - Insurance policies, 1927-1970 (Box 15, Folders 938-941)
    - Expense ledger, 1904-1915 (Box 15, Folder 942)
    - Household expense ledgers, 1928-1960 (Box 15, Folders 943-945)
    - Notes of miscellaneous household and car expenses, undated (Box 15, Folder 946)
    - Bills and receipts, 1908-1929 (Box 15, Folders 947-966)
    - Bills and receipts, 1930-1963 (Box 15, Folders 967-980)
    - Bills and receipts, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folders 981-988)
    - Taxes, 1918-1969 (Box 15, Folders 989-993)
    - Bank notes, 1920-1964 (Box 15, Folders 994-998)
    - Bank statements, 1920-1969 (Box 16, Folders 999-1020)
    - Checkbooks, 1919-1956 (Box 16, Folders 1021-1026)
    - Checkbooks, 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folders 1026A-1026E)
    - Checkbooks, 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folders 1027-1031)
    - Checkbooks, 1960-1968 (Box 17, Folders 1032-1045)
- Series II. Albert Levitt, 1906-1968
  - Subseries A. Correspondence
    - Letters to Albert Levitt
      - General correspondence, 1911-1926; (110 letters) (Box 19, 1113-1123)
      - General correspondence, 1927-1950; (69 letters) (Box 20, 1124-1131A)
      - Letters from Robert W. Claiborne, 1936-1939; (9 letters) (Box 20, Folders 1132-1133)
      - Letters from Alice Paul, 1921-1923; (6 letters) (Box 20, Folder 1134)
      - Letters from Roscoe Pound, 1920-1941; (24 letters) (Box 20, Folders 1135-1136)
      - Letters of introduction for Albert Levitt, 1946; (14 letters) (Box 20, Folder 1137)
      - Letters of recommendation for Alfred Levitt, 1907-1908; (2 letters) (Box 20, Folder 1138)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1921-1926; (61 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1139-1146)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1926 Sep - 1927 Feb; (57 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1147-1154)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1927-1928; (49 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1155-1163)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1930-1935; (87 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1164-1174)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1935 Jun - 1936 May; (63 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1175-1182)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1936-[1938?]; (68 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1183-1190)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1938 Jan - 1940 Mar; (70 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1191-1200)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill, 1940-1957, undated; (86 letters) (Box 19, Folders 1201-1211)
      - Letters from Clara M. Hill, 1925-1959; (25 letters) (Box 21, Folders 1212-1214)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill-Levitt (Leslie Latham), [circa 1932?]-1943; (60 letters) (Box 21, Folders 1215-1220)
      - Letters from Elsie Hill-Levitt (Leslie Latham), 1944-1965, undated; (28 letters) (Box 21, Folders 1221-1223)
      - Miscellaneous family members, 1939-1947; (3 letters) (Box 21, Folder 1224)
      - Personal correspondence [re: his ministry at Willow-Place Chapel], 1912-1914; (11 letters) (Box 21, Folder 1225)
      - Personal correspondence, 1920-1941; (45 letters) (Box 21, Folders 1226-1230)
      - Personal correspondence, 1942-1965, undated; (23 letters) (Box 21, Folders 1231-1232)
      - Letters from Mrs. John Darling ("Mother Mollie"), 1917-1949, undated; (16 letters) (Box 21, Folders 1233-1234)
    - Letters from Albert Levitt
      - General correspondence, 1921-1953, undated; (67 letters) (Box 21, Folders 1235-1240)
      - Levitt Memoranda, 1935-1937; (2 items) (Box 21, Folder 1241)
  - Subseries B. Biographical
    - Army chaplain scrapbooks, 1917-1919 (Box 21, Folders 1242-1244)
    - Articles re Thomas Levet, 1913-1914 (Box 21, Folder 1245)
    - Bibliographies, article lists, circa 1920-1929 (Box 20, Folder 1246)
    - Certificate - Appointment, Special Assistant to the Attorney General, 1933 Jul; (rolled, formerly Box 134) (Box 41)
    - Certificate - Attorney admittance, Court of Appeals of the District of Columbia, 1927; (rolled, formerly Box 134) (Box 41)
    - Certificate - Attorney admittance, Supreme Court of the United States, 1927 Apr; (rolled, formerly Box 134) (Box 41)
    - Certificate - Bar admittance, State of Connecticut, 1928 May; (rolled, formerly Box 134) (Box 41)
    - Certificate - Harvard Law School, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 1247)
    - Certificate - Judge appointment, District Court of the Virgin Islands, 1935; (rolled, formerly Box 134) (Box 41)
    - Certificate - National Geographic Society, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 1247A)
    - Certificates/identification, French passport, foreign residence permit, safe conduct permit, American Army Chaplain certification, Mail Steamer Roma Certificate, 1915-1918 (Box 41, Folder 1248)
    - Diaries - bound books, 1919-1928 (Box 21, Folders 1249-1250)
    - Diaries - bound books, 1929 -1939 (Box 21, Folders 1251-1253)
    - Diaries - bound books, 1940-1956 (Box 22, Folders 1254-1255)
    - Diaries - bound/unbound, 1906-1919 (Box 22, Folders 1256-1266)
    - Diaries - typescripts, personal and office, 1924-1939 (Box 22, Folders 1267-1278)
    - Diaries - typescripts, unbound, 1933-1966 (Box 20, Folders 1279-1288)
    - Diaries - typescripts, unbound, titled "Nationality," originals and carbon copies, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folders 1289-1295)
    - Diaries - unbound, 1935-1937 (Box 20, Folders 1296-1300)
    - Ephemera/identification, including passports, war ration books, 1915-1946 (Box 20, Folder 1301)
    - European travel records, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 1302)
    - Letterhead, business card, circa 1920-1929 (Box 20, Folder 1303)
    - Letters of appointment and resignation, 1933-1936 (Box 41, Folder 1247B)
    - Military Service records, 1908-1919 (Box 20, Folders 1304-1305)
    - Press release, Child Labor, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 1306)
    - Press release, General Assembly in Action, 1931 Apr (Box 20, Folder 1307)
    - Realia - lace from Brussels, Ambulance of the American Hospital of Paris Arm Band, Freemason leather pouch & membership certificate, 1916-1926 (Box 20, Folder 1308)
    - Resumes, CVs, biographical texts, obituaries, 1912-1968 (Box 23, Folder 1309)
    - Unitarian Church, Santa Monica, CA, 1922-1946 (Box 23, Folder 1310)
  - Subseries C. Financial and Legal
    - Checkbooks and check registers, 1926-1951 (Box 23, Folders 1311-1315)
    - Deluth property, bills, receipts, financial correspondence, stocks, bonds, 1920-1959 (Box 23, Folders 1316-1327)
    - Ledger books, some containing correspondence (see 1944 ledger, includes poetry drafts), 1941-1943 (Box 23, Folders 1328-1331)
    - Ledger books, some containing correspondence, 1944 (Box 23, Folders 1332)
    - Ledger books, some containing correspondence, 1945-1948 (Box 22, Folders 1333-1336)
    - Ledger books, some containing correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 22, Folders 1337-1339)
    - Ledger books, some containing correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folders 1340-1341)
    - Ledger books, some containing correspondence, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 1342)
    - Levitt/Hill divorce decree, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 1343)
    - Power of Attorney for Elsie Hill, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 1344)
    - Press clippings, Legal - Levitt v. Black, 1937-1968 (Box 24, Folder 1345-1354)
  - Subseries D. Photographs
    - General, 1912 - [circa 1959] (Box 24, Folders 1355-1356)
    - Meadville Theological Seminary, 1909-1910 (Box 24, Folders 1357-1358)
    - Philippines, photograph album, 1906-1907 (Box 24, Folder 1359)
    - Portraiture, circa 1950-1959 (Box 24, Folder 1360)
    - Walking Trip, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 1361)
  - Subseries E. Clippings
    - General, 1919-1965 (Box 24, Folders 1362-1364)
    - 1928 campaign (Box 24, Folders 1365-1366)
  - Subseries F. Printed Material
    - Barlow, Joel, 1915-1965 (Box 24, Folder 1367)
    - Business and calling cards (includes Coolidge White House invitation), 1922 (Box 24, Folder 1368)
    - Child Labor reports, Dept. of Labor, notes, 1921-1924 (Box 24, Folder 1369)
    - Handbill, "vote dry republican,", undated (Box 24, Folder 1370)
    - HR Bill 4185, native born US women who loose citizenship by marriage to alien, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 1371)
    - Inter American Commission of Women, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 1372)
    - Les Orientales, by Victor Hugo, undated (Box 24, Folder 1373)
    - Unitarian; Court of Appeals, Republican National Committee, Russia, CT Citizen, 1915-1965 (Box 24, Folder 1374)
    - Women/legal, 1921-1924 (Box 25, Folder 1375)
  - Subseries G. Subject Files
    - Barlow, Joel, undated (Box 25, Folder 1376)
    - Book list, private library of A. Levitt and E.M. Hill, undated (Box 25, Folder 1377)
    - Brazil trip, travel documents, correspondence, invoices, itineraries, 1961 (Box 25, Folders 1378-1382)
    - Columbia University, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 1383)
    - Columbia University - lecture, Committee on vacation & resources of working girls, 1908 (Box 25, Folder 1384)
    - Convention of the Independent Republic Party, minutes, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 1385)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, typescripts, 1921-1943 (Box 25, Folder 1386)
    - Harvard Law School, Yale Law School, 1917-1923 (Box 25, Folder 1387)
    - Judgeship - US District Court, District of CT, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 1388)
    - Latham, Louis, undated (Box 25, Folder 1389)
    - Levitt v Black, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 1390)
    - Meadville Theological Seminary, includes scholastic record of A. Levitt, 1908-1920 (Box 25, Folder 1391)
    - Mexico Trip, correspondence, diaries, manuscript, printed materials; re: social, political & business conditions of Mexico, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folders 1392-1396)
    - Ministry at Willow Place Chapel, Brooklyn, NY, 1912-1915 (Box 25, Folders 1397-1398)
    - Political campaigns, 1930-1944 (Box 25, Folders 1399-1400)
    - Programs, musical performances, with notations, 1934-1966 (Box 25, Folders 1401)
    - Right of women to retain maiden names, 1924-1925 (Box 25, Folders 1402)
    - Russia, marriage and labor law, 1921 (Box 25, Folders 1403)
    - Union Settlement House, NY, 1911-1913 (Box 25, Folders 1404)
    - University of North Dakota, 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folders 1405)
    - Washington and Lee University Law School, 1921-1927 (Box 25, Folders 1406)
    - West Bridgewater and Harvard Street Churches, 1916 (Box 25, Folders 1407)
  - Subseries H. Writings
    - A Dagger in Her Heart, 1947 (Box 25, Folders 1408-1409)
    - A Proposed Code of International Criminal Law, undated (Box 25, Folder 1410)